transformyourperformance.com 2009-04-01

# Transform Your Performance - Privacy / Zealise

**Privacy Policy Overview** Zealise Limited is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its website users and customers. We have written this privacy policy to outline the specific information we collect, how we use this information, and what options you have in sharing this information with us when you visit our site. Protecting your privacy is a significant part of our commitment to providing you with a high quality shopping experience.

**Information Collection and Use** We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will never sell, share, or rent this information to others... ever. Zealise Limited collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Links** This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Zealise Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Zealise Limited.

**Newsletter/Bulletin** If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter and/or update bulletin, we ask for the user's email address and name. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**Security** This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or contact information), that information is encrypted and is protected with 128 bit encryption software over an SSL connection. While on a secure page, such as our shopping cart checkout forms, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer is displayed as locked.

**Notification of Changes** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Your Feedback** At Zealise Limited, your privacy is extremely important. If you have any questions about the privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with us, please [Contact Us](http://www.zealise.com/contact.html) and let us know. Thank you.

**Zealise Limited** is a limited liability company registered in England and Wales: Company Number 4690503 VAT Number 806 9702 17. Registered address: Zealise Limited, Oakville House, 9 Meins Croft, Blackburn, Lancashire, BB2 6QH, England. +44 (0) 845 055 8271\. e-mail: info(at)zealise.com (replace the at with @).
